<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Optimization in Image Analysis</title>
    <link>//optimization-image-analysis.compute.dtu.dk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Optimization in Image Analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you wish to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="//optimization-image-analysis.compute.dtu.dk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration</title>
      <link>//optimization-image-analysis.compute.dtu.dk/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//optimization-image-analysis.compute.dtu.dk/registration/</guid>
      <description>To register &amp;amp; pay click this link. If you had registered prior, then use the same e-mail in the purchase system.
Note that your registration is not final until you have paid, The deadline for registration and payment is the 10th of June!
We are limited to 70 spots. In the case we will get fully booked, we&amp;rsquo;ll create a waiting list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program &amp; Speakers</title>
      <link>//optimization-image-analysis.compute.dtu.dk/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//optimization-image-analysis.compute.dtu.dk/program/</guid>
      <description>Program In the making!
Invited Speakers Associate Professor Martin S. Andersen (Publications) Martin Andersen will be giving a general introduction to the subject of optimization to get the summer school of to a great start. Martin’s lectures will cover the basics of optimization and touch upon topics related to his own research. His research focus has been on conic optimization, interior point methods, semidefinite optimization along with implementation of software specifically for convex optimization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading Material &amp; Posters</title>
      <link>//optimization-image-analysis.compute.dtu.dk/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//optimization-image-analysis.compute.dtu.dk/reading/</guid>
      <description>Posters Instructions Full participation in the summer school will give you 3.0 ECTS credits. Full participation requires the student to present a poster at the summer school. This includes:
 Bringing a poster (relevant to the summer school topic, preferably). Max. dimensions are 88cm wide x 126cm tall (A0 portrait). A poster teaser (1-2 slides, 1 minute) at the summer school. Rehears to make sure you are within the time limit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venue &amp; Practicalities</title>
      <link>//optimization-image-analysis.compute.dtu.dk/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//optimization-image-analysis.compute.dtu.dk/venue/</guid>
      <description> Venue Include link and picture
Accomodation What kind of rooms.
Practicalities Transportation Food Drinks Rooms Remember to bring </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//optimization-image-analysis.compute.dtu.dk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//optimization-image-analysis.compute.dtu.dk/about/</guid>
      <description>The summer school is organized in collaboration between The Image Section, Department of Computer Science, University of Copenhagen and the Image Analysis and Computer Graphics section, DTU Compute, Technical University of Denmark.
Co-funding partners  DTU Compute PhD School Imaging and Machine Learning research school (IMLRS)  Organizers  Andreas Aabrandt, aabrandt@di.ku.dk Anders Bjorholm Dahl, abda@dtu.dk Kim Steenstrup Pedersen, kimstp@di.ku.dk Søren Schou Gregersen, sorgre@dtu.dk Gudmundur Einarsson, guei@dtu.dk  ECTS Credits Participation in the summer school will give you 3 ECTS credits if you have full attendance, hand in assignments, and present a poster at the summer school.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>